- 这太快了abc- 我觉得没问题
- It's way too fast.abc- It felt good.
麻烦大家快点清场 谢谢
If we could clear theabcstage quickly,please.
Maury 这太快了
Maury,it's too fast.
- 这跟之前是一样的abc- 那么放慢一点
- It's exactly the same.abc- Then slow it down.
- 一切都好吧 Jeremy?abc- 当然
- Everything all right,jeremy?abc- Sure.
准备好了 随时都可以开始
Ready whenever you are.
从快板开始 谢谢
From the allegro,please.
他有什么问题?
What's his problem?
他的背伤还没完全好
His back's not 100%.
他不能这么和指挥家说话
He can't talk to the conductor like that.
对 他不能 她可以
No,he can't. She could.
你托举没问题吧?
You okay with the lift?
我没问题 除非你没控制好时间
I'll be fine unlessabcyou mess up the timing.
我时间控制得很完美
My timing is perfect.
昨晚你确实控制得很好
It was last night.
关键时刻
Moment of truth.
该死
Damn it.
Penelope 你没事吧?
Penelope,are you all right?
她 她没办法呼吸! 叫医生!
She--she can'tabcbreathe! Call a doctor!
你又打算一整天都不理我?
Are you gonna ignore me all day again?
我帮了你
I help you.
你想杀了Chase
You tried to kill chase.
我做的都是你想做的 只是这样 老板
Doing what you wanted,that's all,boss.
- 我存在abc- 不 你不存在
- I exist.abc- No,you don't.
我承认我的潜意识存在 你可以走了
I acknowledge my subconsciousabcexists. Now go away.
说是一件事 做是另一件事
Saying it is one thing.abcLiving it is another.
你不理性...
You're not rational...
不完全理性
not completely.
把电话听筒放好 把妓女打发走abc穿好衣服 我们有病人了
Put the phone on the receiver,send theabchookers home,and get dressed. We've got a case.
我请了事假
I'm taking a personal day.
纽约芭蕾舞团的21岁明星在台上倒下
21-year-old star at the newabcyork ballet collapsed on stage.
我喜欢芭蕾
I love ballet.
但也许有人提过 我在放事假
But as someone may haveabcmentioned,I'm taking a personal day.
Cuddy说回去上班 不然就炒了你
Cuddy said get yourabcass in or you're fired.
她不会炒了我的
She's not gonna fire me.
即使你不去上班...
She's not gonna fire you...
- 她也不会炒了你?abc- 好吧
- if you don't go to work?abc- Okay.
你觉得我多久才会消失?
How long do you figureabctill I just disappear?
等一等
Hold on.
肺里没有肿瘤和穿孔 没有淤伤abc没有外伤的迹象 也不是性病
No tumors or punctures in the lungs,noabcbruising,no sign of trauma,no stds.
辅助供氧也只能把氧饱和度提到60
And supplemental oxygen's onlyabcgotten her saturation level to 60.
插了胸管 但肺还是在塌陷
Lungs keep collapsingabcdespite a chest tube.
急诊室排除了常规病
E.R.Ruled out the obvious.
白细胞指数和体温正常 所以也不是肺炎
White count and temp wereabcnormal,so no pneumonia.
咖啡煮得一塌糊涂abc13用樱桃味的润唇膏
Coffee's burnt. Thirteen'sabcwearing cherry-flavored lip gloss.
Foreman在盯着你看 这些有帮助吗?
Foreman's staring atabcyou. Any of that helpful?
House?
性病呢?
Std?
我们刚刚说了检查呈阴性abc你觉得我们应该...
We just said the tests wereabcnegative.You think we should--
- 不abc- 她是芭蕾舞演员 会不会是脱水?
- No.abc- She's a dancer. What about dehydration?
会不会是肺挫伤?
What about a pulmonary contusion?
C.T没显示出肺部炎症
C.T.Showed no inflammation on the lungs.
会不会是脱水?
What about dehydration?
尿素氮和肌氨酸酐有升高abc但还在正常范围之内
B.U.N.And creatinine areabcelevated but within range.
嗨 我虽是你大脑里的不理性部分abc但升高就意味着偏高 对不对?
Hey,I'm just the irrational part ofabcyour brain,but elevated means high,right?
脱水可能会隐藏感染
Dehydration could hide an infection.
去治疗她最明显的病症abc静脉输液和抗生素治疗肺炎
Go treat her for the obvious-- I.V.Fluidsabcand antibiotics for the pneumonia.
我们就像是Magic和Kareemabc(80年代NBA湖人队最佳搭档)
We're like magic and kareem.
Pietramala先生 你得了肾癌
Mr. Pietramala,you have kidney cancer.
这是不是很糟糕?abc虽然癌症都很糟 但是...
Is that a bad one?Iabcmean,they're all bad,but--
门关着是有原因的
The door was closed for a reason.
现在开了也是有原因的 我们得谈谈
Well,now it's open for aabcreason. We need to talk.
他 他刚刚说我得了肾癌
H-he just told me I have kidney cancer.
那么你显然需要点时间来接受
Then you'll obviouslyabcneed a moment to process.
House
House.
我在产生幻觉
I'm hallucinating.
我...我很快就回来
I'm... I'll be right back.
我要你旁听我诊断abc审查我做的每件事
I need you to sit in on myabcdifferentials,double-check everything I do.
- 如果这样你不能诊断病人...abc- 也许是睡眠呼吸暂停综合症
- You can't treat patients if--abc- It's got to be sleep apnea.
我好好的睡了一晚 但是我还觉得很累
I get a good night's sleep,andabcI still feel exhausted.
缺乏δ睡眠可能会导致幻觉产生
Lack of delta sleep canabclead to hallucinations.
你有没有其他神经学上的症状?
Do you have any otherabcneurological symptoms?
我没觉得有
I don't think so.
- 失语症?abc- 没
- Aphasia?abc- No.
- 记忆力衰退?abc- 没
- Memory loss?abc- No.
- 易怒?abc- 对 有!
- Irritability?abc- Yeah,that one!
- 别迁怒 他关心你 你关心他abc- 你不该继续工作的
- Don't deflect. He cares about you. You care about him.abc- You shouldn't be practicing.
- 最起码...abc- 够了!
- At least---abc- Enough!
别这么看我 我告诉过你我在产生幻觉
Don't give me the look. Iabctold you I was hallucinating.
你在和谁说话?
Who were you talking to?
一个不是真实存在的人
Someone who's not actually here.
再说这好像没关系
Beyond that seems irrelevant.
你的大脑作出了一个选择abc这能够说明一些事情
Your mind made a choice.abcIt means something.
你知道他会继续问下去的
You know he's just gonna keep asking.
Kutner
Kutner.
真是个不错的选择 他感到难过了
Good choice. He feels bad.
你到底打不打算帮我?
You gonna help me or not?
当然
Yeah.
我可以一周七天都吃这一家做的东西
I could eat from thisabcplace seven days a week.
实际上我们就是这么做的
We practically do.
明晚要不你来点菜 要喝点酒吗?
You can order tomorrowabcnight. Do you want some wine?
不了 谢谢
No,thanks.
我藏有我老公的精子
I have my husband's sperm.
你那个死掉的老公的?
Your dead husband's?
他被确诊的时候我们冷藏的
We froze it when he got diagnosed.
然后你还留着?
And you kept it?
直到现在?
All this time?
我以前觉得如果我没abc找到合适的人 那么...
I used to think if Iabcdidn't find anyone,then--
- 你已经找到了abc- 我知道 但是...
- You found someone.abc- I know,but...
如果我们之间出了问题?
What if it goes wrong?
如果我变成了激进的无政府主义者abc或有第二个家 或者我会返老还童?
What if I turn out to be a-a radical anarchist withabca secret family and that I-I age backwards?
没人想要离婚的
Nobody plans on getting divorced.
我没想过我老公会死 但是他死了
I didn't plan on myabchusband dying. But he did.
那么你 你是说你想要一个婚前协议...
So you--you're saying youabcwant a prenup...
液体形式的
in liquid form.
如果不是睡眠呼吸暂停综合症呢?
What if it's not sleep apnea?
摩托车祸导致的创伤? 滥用维柯丁?
Trauma from your motorcycleabcaccident? Vicodin abuse?
你需要入院治疗
You need to be admitted.
我知道睡眠呼吸暂停综合症的判断是错的abc说明你也知道这是错的
I know you're wrong about sleep apnea,whichabcmeans you know you're wrong about sleep apnea.
你在害怕 告诉他你在害怕
You're scared. Tell him you're scared.
你在这里我睡不着
I can't sleep with you here.
有用吗?
Did it work?
你看我旁边有没有人站着?
Do you see someone standing beside me?
没
No.
那么没用
Then,no.
下一个你准备说是什么病?
So what's next on yourabclist of things it's not?
病人对抗生素没反应 仍然无法呼吸
Patient's not responding to theabcantibiotics. Still can't breathe.
那么做个检查 确认是肺炎
So run a test to confirm it's pneumonia.
我们没办法做支气管镜abc她的肺还在塌陷
We can't do a bronc becauseabcher lungs are still collapsed.
经气管穿刺抽取
Transtracheal aspiration.
那基本上就是水刑
That's basically waterboarding.
- 这很激进abc- 这是个好主意
- It is pretty radical.abc- It's a great idea.
普通激进 House式激进 还是超House式?
Regular radical,me radical,orabcme out of my mind radical?
介于普通和House式之间
Somewhere between regular and you.
那有什么问题?
So what's the problem?
一切都好吧?
Everything okay?
不好 我们的病人无法呼吸
No. Our patient can't breathe.
去做检查 或者想个更好的主意
Either do the test orabccome up with a better one.
我们把范围缩小到感染 外伤abc多发性硬化症 精神分裂症和药物
So we're down toabcinfection,trauma,M.S.,Schizophrenia,or pills.
精神分裂症通常在年轻时就会显现
Schizophrenia usually manifests younger.
这就是把它列在单子下方的原因
That's why it's further down the list.
一个简单的血液测试abc就可以确认是否是感染
I can confirm an infection withabca simple blood test.
感染可以治疗的...治愈的
An infection can be treated... cured.
这意味着你还能工作abc意味着你还能活下去
Means you still got a job.abcMeans you still got a life.
这不是更接近的猜测abc这是让你比较好过的
It doesn't make it a betterabcidea,just a nicer one.
你真是理性的吗?
This the rational you talking?
我没办法自己做
Can't do this on my own.
当我们注入水之后 你会感觉像在溺水
When we inject the water,it'sabcgonna feel like you're drowning.
但是几秒就好了
But it'll be over in a few seconds.
- 然后我会好些吗?abc- 好一点
- Then it'll be better?abc- A little.
把她的肩膀按下去一些
Hold her shoulders down a little.
准备好了吗?
Ready?
你做得很好 我要注入液体了
You're doing great.abcHere comes the liquid.
- Taubabc- 我手滑了
- Taub.abc- I slipped.
- 喔 不abc- 怎么了?
- Oh,no.abc- What?
她的皮肤脱落了
Her skin came off.
她皮肤脱落的速度abc比我们替换人工皮肤还快
Her skin is sloughing off faster than weabccan replace it with the artificial skin.
可能是自体免疫疾病
Could be autoimmune.
抗核抗体检查呈阴性
A.N.A.Was negative.
注意力集中在肺部
Focus on the lungs.
你想让我们无视她失去了80%的皮肤?
You want us to ignore the factabcthat she's lost 80% of her skin?
我们知道不是肺癌
We know it's not lung cancer.
可能是肝肿瘤 扩散到了肺部
Could be a liver tumor,eatsabcthrough to the lungs.
给她的肝做个超声
Get an ultrasound of her liver.
如果发现肿瘤 做个活检
If you find masses,get a biopsy.
我们不能忽略皮肤的问题
We can't just ignore the skin.
这显然是目前最主要 最致命的症状
It's obviously the most significantabcand dangerous symptom right now.
我不认为这是个症状
I don't think it is a symptom.
是我们一手造成的
I think we caused it.
我们干什么了?
By doing what?
我给她开了抗生素
I prescribed antibiotics.
中毒性表皮坏死--abc只有百万分之一的人会有这种反应
Toxic epidermal necrolysis--abcthat's a one-in-a-million reaction.
没错 她就是那不幸的"之一"
Yeah,well,maybe this is the one.
用她本身的皮肤做个拭子检查确认
Get swabs of her old skin to confirm.
你到哪里去了?
Where the hell were you?
我有病人要看
I do have a practice.
芭蕾舞女出现中毒性表皮坏死
Ballerina has toxic epidermal necrolysis.
你确定?
Are you sure?
八九不离十
About to be.
- 太不幸了abc- 我觉得很内疚
- I'm sorry.abc- I feel guilty.
你没做错什么 只是开了抗生素
You didn't do anything wrong.abcYou prescribed antibiotics.
换作任何医生都会这么做
Any other doctor would'veabcdone the exact same thing.
任何医生? 这话真伤人
Any other doctor?abcWords can hurt,you know.
这没道理 我没理由感到内疚...
I have no reason to feel guilty.abcIt doesn't make any sense...
除非我脑子的边缘区域出了问题abc(掌管情绪)
unless there's something wrongabcthe limbic area of my brain.
内疚是个症状?
Guilt as a symptom?
符合多发性硬化症
It's consistent with M.S.
既然血液检查呈阴性abc我得向病人道歉
And since the blood tests wereabcnegative,I have to apologize.
如果能让我好过点 说明你是对的abc我只是在闹情绪 如果不起作用...
If I feel better,then you're right. I wasabcfeeling an emotion. If I feel nothing...
就说明我大脑边缘中招了
it means my limbic brain is shot.
我是House医生
I'm Dr. House.
有人给你解释过病情了吗?
Anyone explain to you your status?
他们在我的肝发现了肿瘤-- 是癌症
They found a mass inabcmy liver--cancer.
他们说是可治愈的abc皮肤也会再长出来
They said they think they can treat itabcand that the skin is starting to take.
我还可以再跳舞
I'll be able to dance again.
她只剩半条人命了 却只惦记着跳舞?
She's half dead,and she'sabcwondering if she'll ever plie again?
顾着小命要紧abc尽情嘲笑她吧
Healthy priorities.abcLet the mocking begin.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我...还没确诊 就按照感染来治疗
I... treated you for an infectionabcbefore confirming that you had one.
导致你的皮肤剥落abc我知道你很痛苦 这是我的错
That's why you lost your skin. I knowabcyou're in pain. I know that I caused it.
对不起
I'm sorry.
做得好
Very nice.
谢谢?
Thank you?
没变化
Nothing.
也许你不是真心的
Maybe you dn't mean it.
我是真心的
I meant it.
你做活检确认了没--
Did you do a liverabcbiopsy to confirm--
没法做 人工皮肤太薄了
Couldn't.The artificialabcskinwas too thin.
会引起出血
She'd bleed out.
为什么你和病人谈话?
Why were you talking to the patient?
我觉得没皮的女人很性感
I think skinless women are hot.
做个经颈静脉肝活检
Do a transjugular liver biopsy.
即使她出血 至少会回到静脉循环
If she bleeds,at leastabcit stays in her veins.
你在征求Wilson同意?
Did you just check with wilson again?
没有
No.
我的感觉没变化 是多发性硬化症
I felt nothing.It's M.S.
道歉会让你好过才怪呢
Apologies aren't supposed toabcmake you feel better.
只会让一般人觉得好过
They're supposed to make theabcother person feel better.
- 我是为了让你好过abc- 好吧
- In orderto make you feel better.abc- Fine.
你想做个腰椎穿刺确认呢abc还是内疚得要去补充维可丁?
You want to do an L.P.To confirm,or isabcguilt enough to start filling prescriptions?
最近的肿瘤离你右侧约1厘米
Last mass about aabccentimeter to your right.
怎么了?
Problem?
阵发性心房扑动abc我们快要完成了
Short burst of flutter.abcWe're almost done.
正在进入右侧肝静脉
Entering the right hepatic vein.
Cameron保存了她前夫的精子
Cameron kept her dead husband's sperm.
她不喜欢你的吗?
She doesn't like yours?
她更喜欢他的
She likes his better.
或者说...
Or at least she...
她想有个保障 以防我哪天...
wants to hang on to it in case mine is...
对她不忠或什么的
unfaithful or something.
前进2厘米
Advancing two centimeters.
你必须让她这么做
You got to let her do it.
否则的话 她这辈子就跟定你了
If you don't,you'll beabcstuck with her forever.
我希望她一辈子跟定我
I want to be stuck with her forever.
她嫁给一个濒死的人
She married a dying guy.
她心理有问题
She has issues.
你永远...也不能离开她了...
You... cannot leave her...
无论发生任何事 因为一旦你这么做abc就不仅是抛弃她的负心人
ever,for any reason,'cause thenabcyou're not just the guy who left her,
还是杀死她孩子的凶手
you're the guy who killed her kids.
心脏搏动异常 退出来
That's not a good rhythm. Get out.
窄QRS波心动过速-- 心跳停止了
Narrow complexabctachycardia--she's gonna crash.
肝活检对癌症呈阴性abc但检查过程中她房颤了
Liver biopsy was negative for cancer,butabcthe procedure sent her heart into a-fib.
不知道是否是活检引发了心脏问题
We don't know it was the biopsyabcthat caused the heart problem.
也许是心脏导致了肺部塌陷
Maybe the heart causedabcthe lungs to collapse.
为什么Wilson在这儿?
Why is wilson here?
你们不是要找癌症嘛
You were looking for cancer.
- 他能帮上忙--abc- 我们没找到癌症
- Thought it'd be helpfulabcif-- - We didn't find cancer.
晓得了 5秒钟前你汇报过了
Yes,which you reported toabcme five seconds ago.
至少让人把凳子坐热了abc才好叫保安把他弄出去
Thought I'd let him finish his hors d'oeuvreabcbefore getting the bouncer to take care of him.
除非心跳回复正常abc否则没法拍片 我们也没法--
Until we can regulate the heart,we can'tabcget any meaningful pictures.So we can't tell--
- 美托洛尔可以治疗心率失常--abc- 试过了 不起作用
- Metoprolol can correct irregularabcheart-- - Tried it. Didn't work.
- 是不是Cuddy让他看着你--abc- 不是
- Is cuddy makingabchim oversee-- - No.
心跳太不正常了 没法做核磁共振abc其它扫描会--
Heart's too irregular forabcmri.Other scans would--
要不然 就是你让他审查你的决定
Then you're makingabchim oversee your choices.
你信不过你自己 为什么?
You don't trust yourself. Why?
Wilson 出去
Wilson,get out.
你确定?
Are you sure?
把你赶出去还要征求你同意吗?
Do I need your approval to throw you out?
你满意了吧?
You happy now?
只有在一种情况下 她的心脏abc才能稳定下来让我们拍片
There's only one time her heart's gonnaabcbe perfectly still for our pictures,
就是她死了的时候
and that's when she's dead.
如果不是多发性硬化症abc只剩下精神病和维柯丁了
If it's not M.S.,Severe mentalabcillness and vicodin are all that's left.
精神病意味着...
Mental illness means...
你再也不能从医了
you can no longer practice medicine.
维柯丁意味着戒断abc你余生都要在痛苦中度过
Vicodin means detox,which meansabcpain for the rest of your life,
结果还是一样 你再也不能从医了
which means you can noabclonger practice medicine.
你是说 我们应该杀死她?
Are you saying we should kill her?
不
No.
我们可以让她的心脏停跳abc拍完片子后再重启
If we stopped her heart,we couldabcget our pictures and then restart it.
要是重启不了怎么办?
What if we cat restart it?
那她只好接着"死"下去了
Then she stays dead.
重启心脏我们驾轻就熟
We restart hearts all the time.
给整个心脏做核磁成像abc需要4分钟时间
It'll take four minutes forabcus to mri her entire heart.
但我们只能做3分钟abc否则会引起脑损伤
And we only have three minutesabcuntil there's brain damage.
你确定要这么做?
You sure about this?
是的
Yeah.
我们要让她的心脏停跳abc然后做个核磁
We're gonna stop herabcheart so I can mri it.
我想这是她的主意
I think it was her idea.
肺炎也是她的主意abc差点没害死病人
Pneumonia was her idea,andabcit almost killed the patient.
- 她?abc- 喔
- Her?abc- Oops.
Kutner的真正身份是女人abc所以他才要自杀
Kutner was secretly a woman.abcThat's why he killed himself.
是Amber
It's amber.
你的潜意识附在我已故女友身上?
Your subconscious pickedabcmy dead girlfriend?
没错 我脑子的非理性部分和abc你脑子的理性部分思考方式一样
Yeah. The irrational part of my brainabcworks like the rational part of yours.
- 这个解释如何?abc- 这...生出了很多问题
- How about that?abc- It... raises questions.
- 这解答了很多问题abc- 谁在乎?
- It answers questions.abc- Who cares?
我的想法相互矛盾abc它们不可能都对
I've got competing ideas.abcThey can't both be right.
每个人都有矛盾的想法abc都会对自己产生怀疑
Everybody gets competing ideas.abcEverybody has doubts.
你说 这做法是普通激进abcHouse式激进 还是超House式?
So is it regular radical,meabcradical,or me out of my mind radical?
这办法够得上终极House式
It's on the upper end of you radical.
没别的方法了么?
Do you have any alternative?
反正我脑子里两个人都没辙了
Nothing that anyone inabcmy head has come up with.
做的时候尽量小心吧
Then you're as safe as you can be.
好极
Great.
你拿到腰椎穿刺的结果了?
You get the L.P.Results back?
是的 出乎意料abc你没得多发性硬化症
Yeah. It's a big shock.abcYou don't have M.S.
但我顺便取了你的血样abc查了维柯丁含量-- 太高了
But while I had your blood sample,Iabcchecked vicodin levels-- way too high.
我需要维柯丁
I need the pills.
这解释真弱 他很清楚abc这根本够不上一个辩解
Not an argument. He knowsabcthat's not an argument.
- 还没排除精神分裂这个可能abc- House...
- It could still be schizophrenia.abc- House...
- 如果你服用精神类药物 就没法从医了abc- 我知道
- if you're on anti-psych meds,you'reabcnot gonnabe able to practice. - I know.
你宁愿做电休克疗法abc都不愿戒掉药瘾?
You'd prefer electroshockabctherapy to rehab?
我只想采取有效的方法
I'd prefer something thatabccould actually work.
- 你这是在逃避abc- 没开玩笑吧
- You're rationalizing.abc- No kidding.
我知道你害怕腿痛abc但电休克疗法--
I know that you're afraid ofabcthe pain,but electroshock--
少给我搬出癌症大夫那套abc同情心泛滥的腔调
Don't give methe cancerabcvoice,that overly earnest tone.
会引发心脏病 中风abc痉挛 致死 甚至更糟
Heartabcattack,stroke,seizure,death,or worse.
还能更糟? 死了再死?
Worse? Double death?
你活下来 但失去了你唯一在乎的东西--abc理性思考的能力
You live,but you damage the only thingabcyou care about-- your rational mind.
我去打几个电话
I'll make some calls.
我会死去?
I'll actually be dead?
只是你的心脏 暂时性地
Just your heart,just for a little while.
但愿如此
Hopefully.
我有个主意
I had an idea.
不要再想馊主意了
Stop having ideas.
胰岛素休克
Insulin shock.
没错 比电休克的危险性少那么一点点abc会让你陷入昏迷
Yes. That's marginally less dangerousabcthan E.C.T.Puts you in a coma.
- 会引起--abc- 能奏效
- Could cause--abc- Could work.
只针对精神分裂 但你根本没有
If you had ychosis,which you don't.
我没腹泻 没出汗 没呕吐abc没有任何维柯丁过量的症状
I've had no diarrhea,no sweating,noabcvomiting,none of the symptoms of vicodin overdose.
没错 除了"看到死人"这点
Yeah,except the "I seeabcdead people" thing.
我嗑药已经好几年了
I've been popping pills for years.
但这几天才看到幻象
I've only been seeing things for days.
有些东西改变了
Something changed.
还是维柯丁的可能性更大
Vicodin addiction is still more likely.
我们不遵从绝对事实了?
So we're no longer dealing in absolutes.
House 我五分钟后过来
House,I'll be up in five minutes.
咱们谈谈为什么你宁愿昏迷都不愿戒药
Then we can talk about how you'dabcrather be in a coma than in rehab.
如果你能在两分钟内赶来abc就帮上大忙了
Actually,if you could be up hereabcin two,that'd be really helpful.
为什么?
Why?
因为我正打算让自己胰岛素休克
'Cause I'm about to putabcmyself into insulin shock.
- 左心房没问题abc- 左冠状动脉也没问题
- Left atrium is fine.abc- Left coronary artery also fine.
- 3分钟快到了abc- 继续
- We're almost at three minutes.abc- Keep going.
- 腱索没问题abc- 右心房没问题
- Chordae tendineae clear.abc- Right atrium is fine.
我要重启她的心脏了
I got to start her back up.
- 还有时间abc- 结束了
- We have some time.abc- We're over.
右冠状动脉没问题
Right coronary artery is fine.
- 3分钟的限制仅是指导数据abc- 她可能撑不了这么久 我们得住手了
- The three-minute threshold is a guideline.abc- She might have less. We have to stop.
大动脉旁的是什么?
What's that by the aorta?
- 我什么也没看见abc- 我要重启她的心脏
- I don't see anything.abc- I'm restarting her heart.
这有个阴影 2厘米--
That's a shadow.abcTwo centimeters--
你觉得害怕abc因为你知道这会起作用
You're only scared becauseabcyou know this is gonna work.
超过3分钟了
We're over three minutes.
来人 拿葡萄糖来!
I need glucose in here!
你差点就挂了
You could've died.
奏效了
It worked.
我的裤子呢?
Where are my pants?
你确定?
Are you sure?
这些天来 她简直无处不在
She's been everywhere I've bn for days.
她不在这 就是说...
She's not here,ergo...
这办法可够不上理智
This was not the next rational step.
到底是谁有成见?
Now who's being biased?
你一心想让我戒断abc甚至超过了我--
You wanted me to detox asabcmuch as I wanted--
我忘记怎么给裤子拉链了
I forgot how to do my zipper.
有没有别的神经缺损症状?
Any other neurological deficits?
你好像没平时那么烦人了
You don't seem to annoyabcmeas much as usual.
不一定是缺陷
Not sure that's a deficit.
并且...我好起来了
And... I'm all better.
- 她真的消失了?abc- 当然
- Is she really gone?abc- Absolutely.
我能感觉到自己正压抑对冒险的冲动
I can feel myself repressing allabckinds of ricky things.
我可以走了吧?
I check out,don't I?
该死
Damn.
他什么也没看到 是伪影
He didn't see anything. Heabcsaw an artifact on the monitor.
她心脏上有阴影
It was a shadow on her heart.
她可以说已经死亡了3分钟
She'd already been technicallyabcdead for three minutes.
我觉得保证她活着abc比延长成像时间更重要
I thought keeping her alive tookabcprecedence over prolonging the photo op.
有脑损伤不?
Any brain damage?
- 没 所有测试都显示--abc- 那显然有更多时间
- No,all tests indicat-- -abcObviously you had more time.
祝你好运
Best of luck.
我想我们不能再杀她一次abc获得更多图片
I assume we can't killabcher again and take more pictures.
- 嗯 你要和Willson谈谈不?abc- 好主意
- Uh,you'll want to check with wilson?abc- Good one.
一定有问题 是病变
It's something,a lesion.
肿瘤 伤痕组织
Tumor,scar tissue.
可能是脓肿 感染
Could be an abscess,infection.
解释了为什么血液中不可见
Explains why it's invisible in the blood.
关起门来搞破坏
It's doing its damage behindabcclosed doors,sealed off.
瞧 猜测的坏处就是 证据支离破碎不足信
See,the problem with speculation is you makeabca spec out of "u" and some guy named "lation,"
我完全不相信
which really doesn't affect me at all.
我们只能猜测 别无他法abc又不能做活检
We have to guess. It's allabcwe've got. We can't do a biopsy.
上次我们试图检查心脏时abc她差点没挺过去
Last time we went into herabcheart,she had a major cardiac event.
那只能...
Which just leaves...
你在找什么?
What are you looking for?
还不知道
I don't know yet.
画面不会改变
The picture doesn't change.
她躺那遭罪
She lies there in pain.
他坐那担心
He sits there worried.
什么都没变
Nothing changes.
我刚有个顿悟...
I just had an epiphany...
全靠自己
all by myself.
就这样出现在脑子里
Popped into my head out of nothing.
想分享下?
Care to share?
他太投入了
He's too devoted.
太投入? 你认为他感到愧疚?
Too devoted? You think he feels guilty?
对 我在挖苦
Right,I'm being cynical.
人们会单纯就是关心abc而非因为出轨后愧疚 理论上正确
People can care because they care,notabcbecause they cheated,theoretically true.
- 但淋病更说得通abc- 不对 没有性病 我们查过了
- But gonorrhea fits better.abc- No. No stds. We tested her.
- 你检查了血液abc- 就该这么检查
- You tested her blood.abc- That is the test.
那不是她的问题所在
That's not where her problem is.
淋病传播到心脏 细菌被包裹在脓肿里
Gonorrhea disseminated to herabcheart,got walled off in an abscess.
- 它不可见abc- 并且...
- It'd be invisible.abc- And...
看上去像块阴影
would look like a shadow.
没必要再次测试abc查查万人迷先生就可以了
No need to test her again,butabcwe can check prince charming.
一旦确证 切除心脏上脓肿
Once you confirm,cut theabcabscess out of her heart.
您的洋葱圈 特别处理过了
Here are your onionabcrings,extra well-done.
谢谢 Molly
Thank you,molly.
有空的话给我再来一杯啤酒 我在庆祝
And another beer when you getabca chance. I'm celebrating.
一个人?
Alone?
谢天谢地是一人
Thank goodness.
不用说了 我是对的
Don't tell me. I was right.
是 她男友得了淋病
Yep. Boyfriend has gonorrhea.
对大家都有好处
And everyone's a winner.
他可很不高兴
He's not too happy about it.
他坚称没有出轨abc一定是从她那传染的
He insists he's never cheated andabcmust've gotten it from her.
难以苟同
Don't think so.
时间上符合
Timing would fit.
他还没有症状 她却快要死了
He's got no symptoms,and she's dying.
谎言也能解释一切
Lying would fit too.
他不再去她病房陪着了
He's not hanging out in her room anymore.
有什么关系呢? 你是对的
What does it matter? You were right.
我们准备给她做手术
We're prepping her for surgery.
我在他身上看到罪恶感
I saw guilt in him.
如果他不是真的感到内疚abc那么不是我对了 而是我侥幸
If he's not actually guilty...abcthen I wasn't right. I was lucky.
House 你做了一个高明的推论
House,you made a brilliantabcdeduction about her heart.
如果我只是侥幸...
And if I was just lucky...
* 尽情享受
* Enjoy yourself
* 时光跑得比想象中快
* it's later than you think
* 尽情享受
* enjoy yourself
* 当你仍青春少艾
* while you're still in the pink
* 岁月匆匆溜走
* the years go by
* 仿佛只是一瞬间
* As quickly as a wink
* 尽情享受
* enjoy yourself
Wilson 来接我
Wilson... come get me.
* 时光跑得比想象中快
* It's later than you think
我知道费城附近有家不错的康复中心
I know a nice facility outside philly.
我和那儿一位医生是同学
I went to undergrad withabcone of the directors.
谢谢
Thanks.
需要几件衣服?
How many shirts do I need?
说是三件就可以 他们有洗衣服务
They said three. They have laundry.
就像又和老妈一起住了 -- 爽啊
Like living with momabcagain-- delightful.
估计是Foreman
It's probably foreman.
他没空
He's unavailable.
病人感染导致败血
Tell her the infection's made her septic.
血压上升前 我们无法切除脓肿
We can't remove theabcabscess until we get her B.P.Up.
输液毫无作用 没有--
And it's not responding toabcfluids. It's not--
他不管这个病例了
He's off the case.
- 病人还好?abc- 恩
- Patient okay?abc- Yeah.
他说谎
He's lying.
为什么我没有恐惧?
Why don't I feel scared?
我看你现在根本无法感知自己的感觉
I'd say you're unaware of whatabcyou're feeling at this moment.
我感觉到很糟
I feel like crap.
生活一塌糊涂 但我感觉不到恐惧...
My life is falling apart,butabcI don't feel scared...
反正不恐惧戒毒
not of the rehab anyway.
我们总能想办法作弊
We've always been able toabcfind a way to cheat.
没用的
It won't work.
这次你想要戒毒起作用
You want it to work this time.
我们想吗?
Do we?
House... 这是你唯一的选择
House... it's your only option.
如果唯一选择没用 我怎么办?
What do I do if myabconly option won't work?
你不能放弃
You don't give up.
要么放弃 要么每6小时电击一次
It's either that orabcelectroshock every six hours.
晚安 Wilson
Good night,wilson.
给她用心肺机如何?
What if we put her onabca heart-lung machine?
病人是败血 我们不需要心肺机
She's septic. We don'tabcneed a heart-lung machine.
我们需要"血液凝聚机"
We need a "blood vessel holderabctogether" machine.
可以尝试高剂量多巴胺
We could try high-dose dopamine.
一种血管收缩剂
It's a vasoconstrictor.
可以关闭血管 以阻止她出血
It'll close the bloodabcvessels so she won't bleed out.
她的心脏无法承受多巴胺 会爆炸的
Her heart can't take thatabcmuch dopamine. It'll explode.
如果不用多巴胺 心脏会内爆
And if we don't use theabcdopamine,it'll implode.
House真不管了?
Is house really done?
听着是
It unded that way.
那就多巴胺
Dopamine it is.
很晚了 我很累
It's late,and I'm tired.
能不能直接进入谈话阶段?
Can we get to the talkingabcpart of this conversation?
我辞职
I quit.
好好
Great.
我保姆7:30下班 所以...
My nanny is off the clock at 7:30,so...
你是要一周假 还是大办公桌...
Your week off,bigger desk...
护士穿紧身衣 或者是其他愚蠢的要求
tighter nurses uniforms,or whateverabcother stupid thing you're about to demand
都必须等到--
is gonna haveabcto wait until--
你大可回去给那小混蛋喂奶abc它不过是你的自我安慰
You can go suckle the little bastard childabcwho makes you feel good about yourself.
你去死
Screw you.
不要
Don't do this.
我有幻觉
I'm hallucinating.
因为维柯丁?
From the vicodin?
其它可能都排除了
Ruled out everything else.
我们可以 嗯...
We can,uh...
让你用化名通过急诊室入院
admit you through theabcE.R.Under a pseudonym.
- 别人不会知道...abc- 我会作弊的...
- No one has to...abc- I'll cheat...
耍花招 想方设法继续用药
scam,find some way to keep using.
那些人很专业
These people know what they're doing.
那些人不了解我
These people don't know me.
- 你了解abc- 她不是你管家
- You do.abc- She's not your keeper.
她没有义务照顾你
She has no responsibility for you.
我需要你
I need you.
我打个电话给保姆
Let me call my babysitter.
- 血压90 60abc- 知道
- Blood pressure's 90 over 60.abc- We know.
我只是强调 还是90 60 维持住了
I'm just saying. It's stillabc90 over 60. It's holding.
脓肿完整
Abscess is intact.
周围组织无感染现象
Doesn't look like any ofabcthe surrounding tissue is affected.
她会没事的
She's gonna be fine.
医生
Doctor.
出状况了
We've got a problem.
躺下 我给你倒杯茶
Lie down. I'll get you some tea.
是啊... 那样我就会好了
Yeah... then I'll be better.
你真以为她没搜查过你藏药的地方?
Do you really think she hasn't searchedabcthis place for your secret stash?
这屋我查过了...
I already did this room...
还有洗手间 你卧室
and the bathroom and your bedroom.
还有哪里 厨房?
Where should I look,in the kitchen?
厨架最上层的咖啡杯
Coffee cup in--inabcthe top shelf.
是个测试啦
That was a test.
我已经查过厨房了
I already did the kitchen.
装得好--abc她会以为你真什么都交出了
Nicely played-- she'll think you'veabccome clean,given her everything.
- 还有abc- 别!
- There's more.abc- Don't!
你够痛苦了 这只会加倍难受
You're hurting already.abcIt'll only get worse.
House 你应该现在告诉我abc因为2小时后 你肯定不想说了
House,you should tell me where it is now,becauseabcyou won't have the will to tell me in two hours.
柜里的鞋子
My shoes in the closet.
我简直不认识你了
It's like I don't evenabcknow who you are anymore.
没事的 握着我手
It's okay. Hold my hand.
我好了?
Am I okay?
我们成功切除了你心脏上的脓肿
We were able to successfullyabcremove the abscess from your heart.
但多巴胺致使你手脚血管收缩坏死
But the dopamine caused the blood vesselsabcin your hands and feet to clamp shut.
我们需要截肢 不然坏疽将蔓延
We need to amputate,orabcthe gangrene will spread.
你会死
You'll die.
我的脚?
My feet?
和手 我很抱歉
And your hands. I'm sorry.
不 我是舞蹈演员
No. I'm a dancer.
坏组织救不回来了
The tissue can't be saved.
不
No.
我们知道House会怎么做
We know what house would do.
House不会等到她醒后征得同意
House would have neverabcwoken her up to ask for consent.
如果不能接受答案 就干脆别问
If you can't live withabctheanswer,don't ask the question.
你是说我们该尊重她选择?
You're saying weabcshould accept her decision?
很大胆 我知道
Bold idea,I know.
也许我们可以让她男友去说服她
Maybe we can get the boyfriendabcto convince her to do it.
是啊 男友要什么有什么
Yeah,boyfriends get everything they want.
别指望了 她男友根本不想再和她说话
Forget it. The boyfriend doesn'tabcwantto talk to her anymore.
- 你去哪?abc- 家 病例结了
- Where are you going?abc- Home. The case is over.
没 还没有
No,it's not.
我们得想出可行的办法
Not until we come up withabcsomething that might work.
不能因为House有乱七八糟的私事abc就任由病人去死了
It's a shame that she might die becauseabchouse has some personal crap to work through.
确切说 病人会死 是因为abcHouse有乱七八糟的私事
Technically,if she dies,it's becauseabchouse has some personal crap to work thugh,
而我们又不够聪明独立 找出答案
and we weren't smart enough toabcget the answer without him.
- 虚惊一场abc- 喝点这个
- False alarm.abc- Drink this.
这就是你的建议-- 喝点这个?
That's yourabcadvice--drink this?
是姜茶 能帮你缓解恶心
It's ginger. It'll ease the nausea.
你知道什么能消除恶心?
You know what would calm the nausea?
维柯丁...大麻... 昏迷
Vicodin... marijuana... a coma.
哦 别装作没看见
Oh,don't pretend you didn't see it.
我看见 说明你也看见了
I saw it,which means you saw it.
打发她走
Send her away.
太苦了
Too bitter.
我够苦了
I already had enough bitter.
我去加点蜂蜜
I'll add some honey.
你真可悲
You're pathetic.
如果想要药 打发她回家就好啦
If you want the pill,just send her home.
但是你不会这么做abc因为这样意味着在她面前承认失败
But yocan't,because that wouldabcbe admitting defeat to her.
现在好玩了
Now,this is interesting.
如果你吃了这药 你就不配得到她
If you take the pill,youabcdon't deserve her.
如果你偷着吃药 你就不配得到任何人
If you secretly take theabcpill,you don't deserve anyone.
不!
No!
不! 不!
No! No!
不会有效的
This isn't gonna work.
可能会有效 所以才要尝试abc血管舒张药能...
It might work. That's all we'reabcgoing for.Vasodilators can--
从再次手术到复活的奇迹
Big jump from reopening to reanimating.
注射完尺骨
I'm out of the ulnar.
我没看到任何改善 不会有效的
I'm not seeing anyabcclearing. This won't work.
可能不会有效
This probably won't work.
- 桡骨动脉很紧abc- 别太快
- Radial artery's really tight.abc- Don't go too fast.
如果血液凝结 她的手就废了
If it clots,she loses the hand.
如果血液凝结 她就死了
If it clo,she's dead.
- 真不可思议abc- 什么?
- I can't believe it.abc- What?
似乎起效了
It might be working.
你能不能...别喘气?
Can you stop? The breathing.
是人都得呼气吐气
Air goes in,air goes out.
那就用鼻子
Hen use ur nose.
按理说你会觉得很难受
You're supposed to feel like crap.
你做得很好
You're doing great.
之后呢?
And after?
你回来上班
You come back to work.
我要不上班呢?
What if I can't?
鸦片依赖会放大痛苦程度
Opioid dependency can make you thinkabcyou have more pain than you really have.
你会挺过去的
You're gonna be okay.
你就信口开河 挑我爱听的说吧
You're telling me what Iabcwantto hear with no evidence.
我说的是我相信的事实
I'm telling you what Iabcbelieve to be the truth.
还不是信口开河
With no evidence.
你可不是什么客观的观察员
You're hardly the most unbiased observer.
你也不是
Neither are you.
我是你医院里最大的资产
I'm your hospital's biggest asset.
你觉得我是因为这才在这的?
Is that why you think I'm here?
就是因为这你才在这 你才骗我说...
It's why you're here. It'sabcwhy you're lying to me about--
20年里我从没骗过你
I haven't lied to you in 20 years.
肯定骗过
Sure you have.
你这话的意思是想告诉我abc你在20年前骗过我什么?
Which means that you just said that because you wantabcto tell me what you lied to me about 20 years ago.
- 你是个混蛋abc- 我说错了?
- You're an ass.abc- Am I wrong?
我不是你内分泌课上的同学
I wasn't in your endocrinology class.
你就坐我边上 我抄你功课...
You sat next to me.abcI cheated off you on--
我是去你的内分泌课旁听
I audited your endocrinology class.
你为什么...
Why wouldabcyou--
因为就算是在那时候abc我都觉得你是个有趣的怪人
Because I thought you were anabcinteresting lunatic even then.
我不是在保护医院财产
I'm not here protectingabchospital property.
只有咱俩在
We're alone.
一晚上都只有咱俩在
E've been alone all night.
不 我是说Amber
No,I mean Amber.
她消失了
She's gone.
Jeremy在哪?
Where's jeremy?
她离开了
He left.
你还好吧?
You okay?
手术见效了
The surgery worked.
恭喜
Congratulations.
我办不到
I can't do it.
你有疑虑
You have doubts.
你没有?
You don't?
没有
No.
这很...
Well,that'S...
天真
naive.
我想下半生都和你在一起 我爱你
I-I want to spend the rest ofabcmy life with you. I love you.
我现在就是这种感觉 但是...
That's how I feel right now,but...
我不能确信
I don't... know.
我会等到你确信
I'll wait until you do.
我没法做到 没人能确保
I ca--I can't know.abcNo--no one knows.
我能
I do.
一会见咯?
I'll see you in later?
你欠我不少报告
I have some papers to push for you.
谢谢
Thank you.
你想吻我 是么?
You want to kiss me,don't you?
我一直都想吻你
I always wantto kiss you.